{
    "subject": "resource/Sir_Charles_Carteret,_3rd_Baronet",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1715",
    "human_readable": "Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet died in 1715.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9554169774055481,
            "question": "When did Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet, die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6043198704719543,
            "question": "What era did Sir Charles Carteret live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5675402283668518,
            "question": "Was Sir Charles Carteret a nobleman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5509095191955566,
            "question": "What was Sir Charles Carteret's title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.519145667552948,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the life of Sir Charles Carteret?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5146836638450623,
            "question": "Who were some notable figures from the same period as Sir Charles Carteret?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4445188641548157,
            "question": "Were there any significant historical events during Sir Charles Carteret's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4008667469024658,
            "question": "What was the significance of the 3rd Baronet title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39659568667411804,
            "question": "Are there any records or historical documents that provide more information about Sir Charles Carteret?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39226657152175903,
            "question": "Was Sir Charles Carteret involved in politics or other public service?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet died in 1715.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2593_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any records or historical documents that provide more information about Sir Charles Carteret?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2593_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the significance of the 3rd Baronet title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2593_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant historical events during Sir Charles Carteret's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2593_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2593_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n\"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet, died in 1715. The text states: \"He died on 3 June 1715 at age 35...\" and also mentions his death on another date (6 June 1715) but confirms that it was in 1715."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Sir Charles Carteret, 3rd Baronet died in 1715.\" Specifically, the document `70.txt` states, \"He died on 3 June 1715 at age 35, without surviving issue.1 He was also reported to have died on 6 June 1715.1\" This confirms that Sir Charles Carteret did indeed die in 1715."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}